Desmond Braxton Jr.

10649 Princeton Street Jamaica, NY, 11435 (347) 279-2605 braxtond232@gmail.com

Adaptable professional with 3+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of Application development for IOS and androids using Kotlin and Swift respectively. Also knowledgable of data communication systems, and web platform development. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the Software Developer role at your company.

EXPERIENCE

TORUS TUTORS, Brooklyn, NY

Piano Teacher/ Math Tutor | Feb 2019 - Present

- Assist students in a variety of subjects; dependent on the needs of the student and the staff we have available.
- Teach students basic classroom skills such as note-taking, studying, and test-taking.
- Use music to strengthen the students understanding and appreciation of Mathematics.
- Have one on one meetings with students' guardians to figure out proper learning plans.

BAMBI DAYCARE CENTER, Jamaica, NY

Administrative Assistant | May 2019 - Aug 2020

- Organize personal information for toddlers using several method; including spreadsheets, databases, word processing and graphic presentation software.
- Partner with legal guardians concerning individual needs of each toddler such as dietary restrictions and health conditions
- Answer telephones, direct calls, and take messages.
- Operate office machines, such as photocopiers and scanners, facsimile machines, voice mail systems, and personal computers.
- Troubleshoot problems involving office equipment, such as computer hardware and software.
- Collect, count, and disburse money, do basic bookkeeping, and complete banking transactions.
- Train other staff members to perform work activities, such as using computer applications.

HOME DEPOT, Jamaica, NY

Sales Associate | Mar 2015 - Jul 2019

- Plan commercial displays to entice and appeal to customers.
- Place prices or descriptive signs on backdrops, fixtures, merchandise, or floor.
- Develop ideas or plans for merchandise displays or window decorations.

EDUCATION

BARUCH COLLEGE

New York, NY

Completed coursework towards Bachelor of Science (B.S.)/ SPA Public Administration (Aug 2014)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Business Level Communication
- Proficiency with several programming languages
- Learning concepts and applying them to other problems
- Problem-solving capability

CERTIFICATIONS

• Mandated Reporter

REFERENCES

David Wilks, CEO Of Torus Tutors, Torus Tutors (347) 300-9723 - tutors265@gmail.com - Former Boss

Tanya Burke, Software Developer, Asana (516) 360-7459 - tanya.burke@hotmail.com - Mentor